His name is Deth. He hunts Trancers. Even in the 20th Century.
Trancers is a science fiction, crime film directed by Charles Band.
Angel City trooper Jack Deth is sent back in time from 2247 to 1985 L.A.
to inhabit the body of his ancestor.
Deth's assignment is to find his archenemy, Whistler, who turns people into zombies, before
the fiend is able to kill all the ancestors of the future's governing council.
Trooper Jack Deth, played by Tim Thomerson.
Leena, played by Helen Hunt.
Hap Ashby, played by Biff Manard.
Martin Whistler / Detective Weisling, played by Michael Stefani.
McNulty, played by Art LaFleur.
Ruth Raines, played by Telma Hopkins.
Trancers (also released as Future Cop) is a 1984 American science fiction action film
directed by Charles Band and starring Tim Thomerson, Helen Hunt, and Art LaFleur.
It is the first film in the Trancers series.
Thomerson plays Jack Deth, a Philip Marlowe-esque police detective from the 23rd
century who travels to the 1980s to bring his old nemesis to justice.
The film portrays a unique method of time travel: people can travel back in time by injecting
themselves with a drug that allows them to take over the body of an ancestor.
The film explores themes of rescue, police, fight, detective, santa claus.
The tone is thought_provoking.